mbsy.co 2017-01-28

# Privacy Policy

OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY

ZFERRAL, INC (“Ambassador”) is committed to protecting your privacy and will make reasonable efforts to provide you a safe and secure user experience. We aim to make our privacy policy easy to read so you that you understand our online data collection practices and usage policies for www.getAmbassador.com (the “Site” and any “Services”). Please note that your use of the Site and any of our Services is subject to our Terms of Service which you may access at the bottom of our homepage. Our Privacy Policy and Terms of Service are integral to your use of our Site, therefore you must agree to both agreements before using our Site or any of our Services.

SCOPE OF THE PRIVACY POLICY

The Privacy Policy applies to all information you provide to Ambassador through the Site. If you have submitted information to any third parties through our Site and Service, we cannot be responsible for any information collected by those third parties.

WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We generally collect two types of information—personally identifiable information (“PII”) and non-personally identifiable information (“Non-PII”). PII is any information that can be used to specifically identify you as an individual. For example, you may submit and we may collect your name, email address, address, phone number, or similar information through the Site. Non-PII consists of information that does not specifically identify you. The following sections describe how we collect and use your PII and Non-PII.

HOW WE COLLECT YOUR INFORMATION

Cookies and Beacons

Like all websites, we use cookies and other technologies, including web beacons, so that we can enhance your user experience. Web beacons and cookies collect information such as URLs you came from and go to, your browser and OS information, your IP address, your mobile provider, your mobile device, and your ISP. None of the information collected by our cookies or web beacons is PII.

Cookies are bits of data placed on your hard drive when you visit websites. A cookie file contains information that can identify you anonymously and maintain your account's privacy. We use cookies to maintain your identity between sessions so that the Site can be personalized based on your preferences or history. We may also use cookies to track information about which pages you visit within the Site to help us gauge the effectiveness of the Site or our content. We may also store other information such as recent searches in your session. We use cookies to tell us, for example, whether you have visited us before or if you are a new visitor, and to help us understand what areas of the Site are of greatest interest to you. Cookies also may enhance your online experience by saving your preferences and password so you do not have to re-enter this information each time you visit the Site. Please be aware that some or all of our cookies may be accessible by third parties.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can configure your browser to stop accepting new cookies, to notify you when you a new cookie is received, and to disable existing cookies. If you choose to disable cookies in your browser, however, you may be unable to take full advantage of all the Site’s features.

Log Files

When you are using the Site, we automatically gather basic information from your browser, such as IP address, browser type, ISP, OS, and date/time stamps to analyze trends, administer the site, analyze bugs, and gather broad demographic information. We will not share log files externally.

Information About You

When you register with Ambassador, we may collect your name, company information and payment information. Some of this information may be viewed by registered users of the Site.

Email/Telephone

When you register for our services we require an email address that may be used for communications. Email messages may contain code that helps our systems track your usage of these emails. We reserve the right to send you email regarding service announcements, administrative messages, and Privacy Policy or Terms of Use changes. We may also contact you by telephone solely in connection with Ambassador services. If you would rather not receive phone calls from us, please remove your phone number from your account.

HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

We will never sell, share, or transfer your information to third parties without your permission. However, you agree that we may use your information:

To enhance or improve our users’ experiences. To understand how you use our Service. To process transactions. To send you email newsletters and respond to inquiries. To register your account and allow you to use our Service. To share with other users. 

THIRD PARTY CONTRACTORS AND OTHER USES

We may use third party suppliers and service providers to facilitate our services, and they may have access to your PII. For example, we may outsource one or more aspects of our Site to a supplier or service provider who performs services according to our requirements. Although we endeavor to select only reputable companies who share our commitment to privacy and will restrict how these suppliers or service providers may use or disclose the PII to which they have access, we are in no way responsible for such third parties or their activities. Therefore, you agree to allow us to give your information to third party suppliers and service providers in order for us to provide service to you. For purposes of transparency, the following is a non-exhaustive list of other entities that we may store, share, or transfer your information with:

Adwords Intercom.io Mixpanel FullContact Salesforce MailChimp Chargify PayPal Dwolla Authorize.net 

Due to factors beyond our control, we cannot fully ensure that your information will not be disclosed to third parties. For example, third parties may circumvent our security measures to unlawfully intercept or access your information.

Search Engines and Web Crawlers

Certain PII that you provide through the registration process (such as name, location, and profile image) may be accessible and made public through syndication programs, search engines, crawlers, and other similar programs.

Required Disclosures

We make every reasonable effort to preserve your privacy, but may need to disclose your PII when required by law or if we have a belief that such action is necessary to:

enforce the Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use; comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process; or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Ambassador, its members, or others. 

You authorize us to disclose any information about you to law enforcement or government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe is necessary or appropriate, in connection with any investigation of illegal activity or that may expose us to liability.

HOW TO REVIEW AND CHANGE INFORMATION

You may control the information you provide to us in various ways. If you would like to change any of your information in our database, you can do so by logging onto your account and following the directions.

To cancel your account, send an email request to privacy@Getambassador.com from the email address you provided us in your registration. We will generally endeavour to remove your user information once we have received a cancellation request, but we cannot guarantee that your information has been or will be removed immediately. After cancellation of your account, you agree that we may retain non-accessible copies of your information for a commercially reasonable amount of time for internal and legal purposes.

AGE RESTRICTIONS

Any person who provides information through the Site represents that they are 18 years of age or older. We do not knowingly collect PII from anyone under the age of 18. Our Site and Service are not designed for users under 18.

CHOICE

You may use your account features on the Site to opt-out of notifications, promotional emails and newsletters. You will also have the ability to opt-in in the event that we share your information with other third-party organizations for their marketing or promotional uses or various other programs or features. If you wish to be removed from any communications simply respond to the link provided in the email or email us at privacy@Getambassador.com.

THIRD PARTIES

Ambassador or others may post links to third party websites on our Site or Service, which may include information that we have no control over. When accessing a third party site through our Site or Service, you acknowledge that you are aware that these third party websites are not screened for privacy or security issues by us, and you release us from any liability for the conduct of these third party websites.

Please be aware that this Privacy Policy, and any other policies in place, in addition to any amendments, does not create rights enforceable by third parties. Ambassador bears no responsibility for the information collected or used by any advertiser or third party website. You must review their Terms of Service and Privacy to understand how their information collection practices work.

CONTACTING US

If you have any questions or comments about the Privacy Policy, the practices of the Site, or your experiences with the Site, please contact us atprivacy@Getambassador.com.

PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES

We reserve the right to change or update the Privacy Policy at any time, and will notify users of the Site by posting such changed or updated Privacy Policy on this page. Under certain circumstances, we may also elect to notify you of changes or updates to the Privacy Policy by additional means, such as by posting a notice on the homepage of the Site or by sending you an email. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to the Site and will be reflected by the Effective Date below. Continued use of the Site following any changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to the Privacy Policy and any future revisions.

SECURITY

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting profile access. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times.

The Site uses SSL certificates to help secure your information. However, as this is the internet we can make no assurances or guarantees that your information will be 100% safe. For this reason we recommend you take appropriate measures such as protecting your passwords, using firewalls or downloading anti-virus software. If we learn of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically through our Site or by email so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using the Site or providing personal information to us, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of the Site.

INTERNATIONAL USERS

The Site is hosted in the United States. All information that is submitted by you is stored and processed within the US, which may not have the same data protection and privacy laws as your country. For your personal information, you agree to:

the use of your personal data for the uses identified above in accordance with the Privacy Policy; and the transfer of your personal data to the United States as indicated above. 

Please be aware that your information may also be processed by us in the country where it was collected as well as other countries where laws regarding processing of information may be less stringent than the laws in your country.

CHANGE OF CONTROL

In the event of a change of control of Ambassador from, for example, a sale to, or merger with, another entity, or upon Ambassador’s filing for a bankruptcy, information Ambassador receives from you is a Ambassador asset that may be transferred.

CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

Ambassador permits residents of the State of California to use its Service, and complies with the California Business and Professions Code §§ 22575-22579. If you are a California resident you may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to any third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Various provisions throughout this Privacy Policy address requirements of the Californian privacy statutes. Although we do not disseminate your information to third parties without permission, you must presume that we collect electronic information from all visitors. You may contact us at privacy@Getambassador.com with any questions. 

Last updated: July 25, 2013
